The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
2 years later
Rank 3 demonic energy is equivalent to Foundation Establishment.
10 times that is Core Formation.
If I extrapolate,
Soul Transformation requires rank 30 000.
I barely have enough celestial jades to reach Late stage Soul Transformation.
Using this demonic energy and converting it to celestial spiritual energy
is currently my best method to breakthrough to Ascendant.
In these 2 years,
the tribe has grown considerably.
It's really crowded now.
The souls within their Soul Flags need to be nurtured many times
to reach their full power.
Instead of teaching them how to nurture the souls,
I might as well put the Billion-Soul Flag here as a defensive formation.
Soul Refining Tribe,
release your souls into the black clouds
twice a day.
It will temper your souls.
Thank you, Ancestor,
for giving us this divine technique !
Brother Thirteen,
what does it feel like to cultivate the Soul Refining spell ?
Why do you ask him ?
He's crippled.
He doesn't even talk anymore.
Everyone, run ! There's a demon beast !
Everyone, run !
Run !
Brother Thirteen...
Ancestor,
when Thirteen was hunting,
he encountered a rare demon beast
By the time I arrived,
it was already too late.
I understand,
you may leave.
Let's go.
His meridians are shattered
but how could he have demonic energy of rank 2 ?
He forcibly absorbed demonic energy to store it inside his flesh.
It must have been excruciatingly painful
but he endured it for 2 whole years.
His determination is undeniable.
But with his meridians shattered,
the only thing that can save him now
is the Ancient God Tactic.
But this technique...
isn't something I can give so easily.
Thank you Ancestor, for saving my life !
You forcibly absorbed demonic energy.
Do you know the more you absorb,
the closer you are to death ?
Thirteen knows.
But I just thought that
by forcibly absorbing demonic energy,
I might still have a sliver of a chance to cultivate.
I don't want to be useless to the tribe
or to the Ancestor !
I can give you a body refining method
that will allow you to assimilate demonic energy into your flesh.
Although you won't be able to use spells,
your body will become stronger and stronger.
This body refining method is extremely painful.
If you mess up, even I might not be able to save you.
Can you withstand it ?
Thirteen
will definitely not let the Ancestor down !
I'm very familiar
with that look in his eyes...
If he can cultivate the Giant Demon Clan's body refining method,
I will teach him the first layer of the Ancient God Tactic.
It all depends on his fate.
We pay respects to the Ancestor.
This child is the one I mentioned before, Hu Pao.
He was born with rank 2 demonic energy.
In just a few short months,
he has already refined 13 Soul Flags.
Greetings, Ancestor.
Hu Pao\NSoul Refining Tribe
Hu Pao has already cultivated the Soul Refining spell to the fourth stage
and I have 5 primary souls.
Ancestor, have a look.
Don't disrespect the Ancestor !
This child is extremely talented.
He might be even more talented than Red Butterfly.
If we let him grow freely within the tribe,
he might cause trouble in the future.
You will cultivate by my side.
Hu Pao pays respects to Master !
The Soul Refining Tribe is here !
Now surrender peacefully !
Those who lay down their arms
will be spared !
Soul Refining Tribe,
deploy our great formation !
The Holy Soul Refining Sect
shall live forever !
4 years ago,
I wasn't in a hurry to join Ancient Demon City's army
because I didn't have a foothold.
Now that the Soul Refining Tribe's influence is established,
it's time to leave.
From now on,
the Soul Refining Tribe will cease to expand.
You shall cultivate with all your might.
Ouyang Hua,
if the tribe encounters danger in the future,
use this jade slip to send me a message.
Junior will fulfill his duty !
We bid farewell to the Ancestor !
Ancient Demon City\NDemon Spirit Land
Long time no see.
Let's go, let's go.
Where is the commander of this place ?
Where did those savages come from ?
The Commander is not someone you can meet like that !
Scram !
How dare you !
You dare to attack Ancient Demon City !?
Presumptuous !
That punch...
was wrong.
Thirteen was reckless.
But in my eyes,
anyone who disrespects the Ancestor
is an enemy.
I mean your punching technique was wrong.
You used all your strength but 40% of the power was lost
because you weren't able to control your heart.
With your current strength,
that demon soldier wouldn't have withstood the blow.
You're courting death !
Watch carefully
how I punch.
Although body refining is different from spells,
being in control is still the crux.
On the cultivation path, only the strong reign supreme.
Remember,
don't be belligerent
but never fear battle.
We pay respects to Commander Yao !
The Blood Ancestor's daughter...
This Yao Xixue always acts domineeringly.
She doesn't have good intentions.
Wang Lin,
I presume you've also come
to Ancient Demon City in order to gain military merits.
The Demon General ordered you
to follow me.
Given this woman's arrogance,
she wouldn't willingly relay messages like that.
The Demon General who defeated her
must be extraordinarily powerful.
Wait for me in the city.
Understood !
Left Wing Demon General's Manor\NAncient Demon City
Over 10 Soul Transformation cultivators
and many are at Late stage...
I saw in Luo Yun's memories that this Demon General
has subdued many Soul Transformation cultivators
and has never been defeated on the battlefield.
He must be a powerhouse who has reached Ascendant.
Your Excellency,
I have brought him here.
Mo Lihai\NLeft Wing Demon General\NRank 200 000 demonic energy\NPeak Late stage Soul Transformation
The foreigner that attacked my demon soldiers
outside the wall...
was it you !?
I was wrong.
This person's cultivation hasn't reached Ascendant.
If he's only Peak Late stage Soul Transformation.
Then how did he manage
to remain undefeated for thousands of years in the Demon Spirit Land
and subdue so many powerful cultivators ?
It was me.
Then let me see
what kind of skills you have !
Death Finger !
With this finger,
you can become an Elder of my manor.
Demon Spirit Land has inner and outer positions.
Only the outer positions like Commander
and Chief Commander
can command troops
and obtain military merits.
I don't want
an inner position.
You actually know the difference between inner and outer positions ?
As long as your strength is sufficient,
you foreigners can obtain any outer position.
But that finger from before...
is not enough !
You may continue.
It's this move...
It's coming.
This is my Ten Collapse Battle Intent.
If you withstand 8 collapses,
you will be a Commander.
Withstand them all
and you will be a Chief Commander !
First collapse,
Mountain Crusher !
How many collapses do you think he can take ?
The Ten Collapse Battle Intent can shake the world.
This person's strength is mediocre
so I think no more than 2 collapses.
Demonic Finger !
Such a powerful spell !
Second collapse,
Cloud Splitter !
This second collapse uses the momentum of the first one
to be 10 times stronger.
If I fought to the death,
I'd have to use the Underworld Finger or the God Slaying Chariot.
But there are many powerful experts here,
I can't play all my cards now.
If I can't face it head-on,
then I might as well attack
and seize the initiative.
Celestial Slaughter Art !
Very good !
Under my Battle Intent,
you're one of the few that fights back.
Let's see if you can break the remaining 8 collapses !
Third collapse,
Tide Breaker !
Another tenfold increase in strength...
how can he unleash spells that exceed his demonic energy cultivation !?
Impressive !
But it all ends here.
Fourth collapse...
Star Shatterer !
The Ten Collapse Battle Intent is extremely domineering.
With my cultivation,
I could only withstand up to the fifth collapse.
If it weren't for the artifact my father gave me,
I wouldn't have gotten the Commander position.
It's normal for Wang Lin
to give up here.
Resisting the fourth collapse is no easy feat.
Back down
and you can become an Elder.
Faith...
Your Ten Collapse Battle Intent
is a spell born from faith.
Interesting...
The Ten Collapse Battle Intent
doesn't come from his demonic power cultivation
but from his long-held faith in certain victory on the battlefield.
This move has defeated countless cultivators over thousands of years.
Each victory solidified his faith in victory,
ultimately creating this Ten Collapse Battle Intent with each collapse stronger than the last.
If he keeps winning with this faith in victory,
his Ten Collapse Battle Intent will continue to evolve
endlessly.
But since it's just faith,
then there is one thing I can use.
Demonic Finger...
Your Dao is fundamentally different from mine,
if you want to truly grasp the essence of the Demonic Finger,
you must transform into a demon.
You're the first to ever have a breakthrough during my Ten Collapse Battle Intent.
How interesting !
Let me see
how much progress you've made.
Fifth collapse,
Soul Turner !
Why is my Battle Intent
becoming unstable ?
I'm seizing your wisdom
to break your Dao.
Although your faith is strong,
my demonic thoughts can break it.
Sixth collapse,
Wheel Stopper !
The key to breaking your Ten Collapse Battle Intent
isn't cultivation
but a contest of faith !
Not bad !
I, Mo Lihai, have roamed battlefields
and been victorious for thousands years !
With what faith do you expect to defeat me ?
Seventh collapse,
Calamity Annihilation !
One finger...
to become a demon !
Mo Lihai...
was forced back !
So thrilling !
Wang Lin,
I really underestimated you !
Prepare for the last 3 collapses !
Let's see which one of us
has the strongest faith !
The demonic thoughts are too strong...
They nearly devoured my Dao Heart.
If I transform into a demon,
then even if I win, the loss would outweigh the gains.
Demon General,
I forfeit.
Such intense demonic thoughts
aren't even your true Dao Heart ?
You know when to retreat
and you understand when to make the right decision.
Good !
Although you didn't break the 10 collapses,
with your strength, you are qualified to become a Commander.
I appoint you today as Commander,
you will command 10 000 demon soldiers.
You can return to the city.
In 7 days,
someone will take you to your assigned barracks.
Thank you, General.
This person entered the manor as a nobody
with his Middle stage Soul Transformation cultivation,
but he was able to become a Commander all by himself...
As the mosquito beast rushed across the sky, every tribe it passed activated their protection formation. In their eyes, the mosquito was simply too strong. It was already creating sonic booms just by flying across the sky. The thunderous roars it let out made it seem like thunder was descending upon the earth, creating an overall very shocking scene.\N\NBefore, when Wang Lin first entered the Demon Spirit Land, he didn’t know about the existence of the formations and tribes. The formations also had the ability to hide the people within, so he wasn’t able to find anyone. However, now he had a certain understanding of the Demon Spirit Land, so looking down now, he saw countless tribes.\N\NThere were strong and weak, large and small ones, and the population varied greatly between the tribes.\N\N“If my Soul Refining Tribe can unite all of the tribes in the Demon Spirit Land, it will become a force that will even shock the nine countries here!” Wang Lin’s eyes became cold.
I've been walking this path for endless years
just to catch a glimpse of your silhouette.
Is it the compass of fate
that wrote this outcome for us ?
The heavens want to erase your existence,
that's the obsession guiding me.
Is this the path to uncover
truths from falsehoods ?
In a world of murk and shadow,
only the flame of truth can light the way.
Look at them all,
being carried by the waves.
being drowned.
I don't want to believe in whoever decides fate,
I will let the world refine my soul.
So what if I become an Immortal and defy the heavens ?
I will fight.
I'll break through the abyss of despair
to finally learn who I really am.
My body is stained by the bloody color of slaughter,
I embrace this obsession.
I won't glance back at the wasteland I left behind.
Even if this suffering shatters my soul
and I'm reborn countless times in hell,
I'll still fight.
It's hard to avoid loneliness
when you are above everyone else.
Can a moth that has witnessed the flames of a Suzaku
be afraid of a firefly ?